moonboy.in 2017-03-14

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

**Registration Obligations**

MBIPL (Moonboy International Pvt Ltd) respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides you with the details in the manner your data is collected and used by us. You are advised to please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

This Privacy Policy describes the information, as part of the normal operation of our services; we collect from you and what may happen to that information. Although this policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about our practices so that you can make informed decisions.

By accepting the Privacy Policy during registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Privacy Guarantee**

We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent and we only use your information as described in the Privacy Policy. We view protection of your privacy as a very important community principle. We understand clearly that you and Your Information is one of our most important assets. We store and process Your Information on computers located in the India that are protected by physical as well as technological security devices. Periodically we may reveal general statistical information about our site and visitors, such as number of visitors, number and type of goods and services purchased, etc.

**Information Collected**

As a policy we only collect details that have been provided by you on registration. We may collect additional information with reference to your participation in our promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provided by you while giving feedback or while completing profile forms.

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you like:

  1. Name including first and last name.
  2. Mobile phone number and contact details.
  3. ZIP/Postal code.

We use contact information internally to:

  1. Direct our efforts for product improvement.
  2. Contact you as a survey respondent.
  3. Send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers.

**Our Disclosure of Your Information**

We will not use your personal information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you.

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless:

  1. We have your permission.
  2. To provide products or services you've requested.
  3. To help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person, violations of MBIPL terms of use or to defend against legal claims.
  4. Special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure.

**Retargeting Privacy Policy**

**Steps for user to OPT-OUT of setting website cookie on users browsers**

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies of disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Information about   _Non Personally Identifiable Information_   advertising like behavioural targeting and/or retargeting**

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process.

**Steps to OPT-OUT of NPII advertising**

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third party service provider, please write to us at  _info@moonboy.in_

**Security**

To protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, we have in place appropriate procedures. We will endeavor to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information; transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

**Policy update**

We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this Site.

Your Consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Site. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

**_INFORMATION LIABILITY_**

In no event shall MBIPL or any of its sources be liable for any direct, special, incidental, indirect, or consequential damages whatsoever (including but not limited to: damages for loss of business profits, business interruption, loss of business information, or any other pecuniary loss) arising out of the use of the information made available on this web site.

Information on the moonboy.in web site may not be reproduced, copied, or altered without the express written consent of MBIPL and its affiliates.

**_Termination_**

MBIPL may terminate this Agreement and these terms and conditions and/or the provision of any of the services at any time for any reason, including any improper use of this portal or your failure to comply with these terms and conditions. Such termination shall not affect any right to relief to which MBIPL and its third party providers and distributors may be entitled, at law or in equity. Upon termination of this User Agreement and these terms and conditions, all rights granted to you will terminate and revert to MBIPL and its third party providers or distributors, as applicable.

**_No resale of service_**

You agree not to reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell or exploit for any commercial purposes, any portion of the Service, use of the Service, or access to the Service.

**_DISCLAIMERS OF WARRANTIES & PRODUCT LIABILITY_**

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL ‘S ROLE IS THAT OF AN INTERMEDIARY IN THE FORM OF AN ONLINE MARKETPLACE AND IS LIMITED TO MANAGING THE WEBSITE TO ENABLE SELLER TO EXHIBIT, ADVERTISE, DISPLAY, MAKE AVAILABLE AND OFFER TO SELL THE PRODUCTS AND TO ENABLE BUYER TO PURCHASE THE PRODUCTS SO OFFERED, AND OTHER INCIDENTAL SERVICES TO FACILITATE THE TRANSACTIONS BETWEEN SELLERS AND THE BUYERS. ACCORDINGLY, THE CONTRACT FOR SALE OF ANY OF THE PRODUCTS SHALL BE A BIPARTITE CONTRACT BETWEEN SELLER AND THE BUYER. AT NO TIME SHALL MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL HAVE ANY OBLIGATIONS OR LIABILITIES IN RESPECT OF SUCH CONTRACT NOR SHALL MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL HOLD ANY TITLE IN THE PRODUCTS. THE TITLE IN THE PRODUCTS AND OTHER RIGHTS AND INTEREST IN THE PRODUCTS SHALL DIRECTLY PASS TO THE BUYER FROM THE SELLER.

THESE TERMS OF SALE SHALL NOT AMEND OR MODIFY ANY AGREEMENTS, CONTRACTS, TERMS OR POLICIES BETWEEN THE BUYER OR SELLER ON ONE HAND AND MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL ON THE OTHER HAND.

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL DOES NOT CONTROL, ENDORSE OR ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY PRODUCT (INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PRODUCT CATALOGUES) OFFERED BY SELLERS ACCESSIBLE THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED SITES. MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER ABOUT, AND SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR, THE SELLER OR ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES, THEIR PRODUCTS INCLUDING REPRESENTATIONS RELATING TO MERCHANTABILIGY, FITNESS OF A PRODUCT OR SERVICE FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD PARTY INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS. ANY TRANSACTIONS THAT BUYER MAY HAVE WITH SUCH THIRD PARTIES ARE AT Buyer's OWN RISK. THE PRODUCTS SHALL BE SUBJECT TO SELLER'S TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR WARRANTY, SERVICE AND MAINTENANCE, AND MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL DOES NOT ACCEPT ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE SAME. MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL ALSO DOES NOT ACCEPT ANY RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE USAGE OF THE PRODUCTS BY THE BUYER.

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO ANY ILLEGAL, INFRINGING, FAKE, DUPLICATE, SPURIOUS, DEFECTIVE OR COUNTERFEIT, REFURBISHED, EXPIRED PRODUCTS PURCHASED BY BUYER FROM THE SELLER AND MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL SHALL NOT ASSUME ANY LIABILITY IF THE PRODUCT PURCHASED OR AVAILED BY BUYER FROM THE SELLER IS NOT EXACTLY AS PER SPECIFICATIONS DETAILED IN THE PURCHASE CONFIRMATION ORDER.

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL is in no way responsible or liable for the offer for sale or sale of the Product by the Seller to the Buyer, its delivery, the warranty terms (if any) related to the Product and the return, refund or cancellation of purchase of any Products.

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL does not warrant that the sale price provided by the Seller of the Product is accurate, proper and valid. Any error in the sale price shall be solely attributed to the Seller and not to MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL. Prices, Product description and availability of the Product are Seller's responsibility.

Buyer expressly acknowledges that the Seller selling the defective Product will be responsible to Buyer for any claims that Buyer may have in relation to such defective Product and MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL shall not in any manner be held liable for the same.

MOONBOY INTERNATIONAL shall not assume any liability for the non-availability of the Product, delivery of the Product directly by the Seller and the installation of the Product where required.
